

# KANUPRIYA **JAMWAL**

kanupriyajamwal15@gmail.com



Dublin, Ireland



## **ABOUT**

I enjoy developing creative technical and design solutions to human problems. I like to embrace our lightning paced industry as it lets me push myself and continue to strive for better products, services and experiences. I get excited about analysing, brainstorming, ideation and learning.

## kanupriyajamwal.github.io

# **EDUCATION**

### **University College Dublin**

**Class Representative** 

MSc. Human Computer Interaction 2023 – 2024

**Certification** - Google UX Design Course 2022

### NMIMS School of Technology

BTech. Computer Engineering 2016 – 2020

# **SKILLS**

- Well-versed in design principles and product management strategies
- Proven ability to foster collaboration within multidisciplinary teams
- Limitless passion for brainstorming, ideation and learning
- · Focused on inclusive and accessible work
- Skilled in simultaneous task management
- Fluent in several design tools and programming languages

# WORK EXPERIENCE

### **Product Manager**

Creator Club | June 2024 - Present

- Working with founder to define product vision
- · Creating a product strategy and roadmap

### **Student Designer**

Chronic Pain Ireland | Summer 2024

• End-to-end delivery of design Solution for individuals suffering from chronic pain

#### Senior Software Analyst

Capgemini | 2020 - 2023

- Customised enhancements on SAP Advanced Track and Trace for Pharmaceuticals (ATTP) for client.
- Coordinated with internal developers, third party development teams and clients to deliver product.
- Trained new colleagues in SAP ATTP system
- Ran Root Cause Analysis to find appropriate support solutions

**Past Internships -** Brand and Web Design Intern, Ideation and UX Designer, Information Technology Intern

# HIGHLIGHTS

**Strategy and design work** - Job recommendation system, Menu & recipe apps, 2 player game, Band website, Derailment prevention system for railway, ATM for kids

**Research** - AI (various topics), Pegasus, Transmedia storytelling, Doomscrolling, Asexual dating app **Data Representation** - Poster work for quantitative analysis, research plan and academic papers **Other Projects** - Podcast, Image restoration tool, Information Behaviour Study